mattters.com 2013-08-06

# Privacy - Mattters: Start enjoying the news...

## Mattters Privacy Policy

Mattters is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Mattters Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Mattters website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. Unauthorized use of this system is prohibited. Usage may be subject to security testing and monitoring. Misuse is subject to criminal prosecution; and no expectation of privacy except as otherwise provided by applicable privacy laws.

Collection of your Personal Information

Mattters collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Mattters also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Mattters. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Mattters for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Mattters Web site.

Mattters encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Mattters so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Mattters is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Mattters and Mattters family of Web sites.

Use of your Personal Information

Mattters collects and uses your personal information to operate the Mattters Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Mattters also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Mattters and its affiliates. Mattters may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Mattters does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Mattters may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Mattters may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, or provide customer support. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Mattters, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Mattters does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Mattters keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Mattters, in order to determine what Mattters services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Mattters to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Mattters Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Mattters or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Mattters; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Mattters, or the public.

Use of Cookies

The Mattters website uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Mattters pages, or register with Mattters site or services, a cookie helps Mattters to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, favorite pages, and so on. When you return to the same Mattters Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Mattters features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Mattters services or Web sites you visit.

Security of your Personal Information

Mattters secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Mattters secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Changes to this Statement

Mattters will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Mattters encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Mattters is protecting your information.

Contact Information

Mattters welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Mattters has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Mattters at: 

We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
